Guide to the Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection 1860-2010 MSS.292
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Audio
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - "Asian American Reality conf." Sunday 12/6/70 [B...] Lee Boggs - Roll 3 side A, Roll 3 side B, 1970 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0005)
    - "Between the Wars: War Comes at Pearl Harbor"; "The Purple Plain" (incomplete), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0006)
    - "The Bitter Tea of General Yen", Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0007)
    - [Black Perspective on the News], Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0008)
    - "Charlie Chan in Panama" (1940), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0009)
    - "Charlie Chan in Paris" (1935), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0010)
    - "Charlie Chan in Paris" (A), "I'm Going to be a Lion's Head"; "Bird of Passage" (B), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0011)
    - "Charlie Chan on Broadway" (1937) fragments (A); "If Tomorrow Comes" (1971) - final part; The World of Suzie Wong" (1961) - opening only (B), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0012)
    - "Charlie Chan's Murder Cruise" (1940), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0013)
    - "China Girl" 1942 (last part only); "To Kill a Dragon" 1967 (part only) (A); "To Kill a Dragon" cont.; "The Good Earth" 1936 (B), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0014)
    - "Chinatown: A Place to Live" (1978) (A); "From Hell to Eternity" (1958), part 1 (B), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0015)
    - Cohen tape [1] 7/21/1989 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0016)
    - Cohen tape [2] 7/23/1989 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0017)
    - "Dragon Seed" (1944) part 1, Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0018)
    - "Dragon Seed" (1944) part 2, Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0019)
    - "From Spikes to Spindles" (1976) (A); "The Letter" (1929) (B), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0020)
    - Hiroshima - Nagasaki, Sunday 7/30/72, 1972 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0021)
    - How the West Was Won, "China Doll" part A & B, 1979 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0022)
    - How the West Was Won, "China Doll" part C, Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0023)
    - "If Tomorrow Comes" (1971) (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0024)
    - "If Tomorrow Comes" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0025)
    - Interview with Sab Shimono 6/29/74 - Roll 1 / 2, 1974 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0026)
    - Interview with Sab Shimono 6/29/74 - Roll 2 / 2, 1974 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0027)
    - "King Kong" (1933), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0028)
    - Kojak - "Chinatown Murders" (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0029)
    - Kojak - "Chinatown Murders" (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0030)
    - "Kung Fu" (1972), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0031)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Cassette needs preservation. When processed, was being held together with scotch tape, which has since been removed.
    - "Madame Butterfly" (1932) - includes music, 1978 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0032)
    - NBC News - "Chinatown or Bust" 3/20-21/1973 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0033)
    - "New York Illustrated: Chinese New Yorkers: A New Generation" (Jan. 14, 1972) (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0034)
    - "Old San Francisco" (Killiam Version), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0035)
    - "Our Story" (5/10/76), 1976 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0036)
    - Samurai (A); Barney Miller (B), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0037)
    - "Satan Never Sleeps" (1962) part II, Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0038)
    - "Satan Never Sleeps" part III; "Tora, Tora, Tora" last part only; "Halls of Montezuma" (1951) excerpts only (A); "Halls," cont.; "Charlie Chan on Broadway" (1937) excerpts only (B), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0039)
    - "Seven Women", Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0040)
    - "Shanghai" (1935) (A); "The Vengeance of Fu Manchu" (1967) (B), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0041)
    - "Shanghai Gesture" (1932), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0042)
    - "Sugimoto" transcription of exhibit opening 2/27/78, 1978 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0043)
    - "Thirty Seconds Over Tokyo" (1944) excerpts, Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0044)
    - "Vengeance of Fu Manchu" (cont.) (A); "Satan Never Sleeps" part I (B), Undated (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0045)
    - "Year of the Dragon (Police Story) part 1, 1975 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0046)
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Pace College, NYC 12/6/70 - tape 1, side A, part 1, Undated (Box 78, Disk ID: 292.0047)
      Format: CD-R
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Pace College, NYC 12/6/70 - tape 1, side A, part 2, Undated (Box 78, Disk ID: 292.0048)
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Pace College, NYC 12/6/70 - tape 1, side B, part 1; tape 2, side A, Undated (Box 78, Disk ID: 292.0049)
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Pace College, NYC 12/6/70 - tape 3, side A, part 1, Undated (Box 78, Disk ID: 292.0050)
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Pace College, NYC 12/6/70 - tape 3, side B, part 1, Undated (Box 78, Disk ID: 292.0051)
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Pace College, NYC 12/6/70 - tape 3, side B, part 2, Undated (Box 78, Disk ID: 292.0052)
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Pace College, NYC 12/6/70 - tape 3, side B, part 3, Undated (Box 78, Disk ID: 292.0053)
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Roll #1, 1970 (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0054)
      Format: 1/4" Audio Reel
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Roll #2, 1970 (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0055)
    - Asian American Reality Conference - Reel #3, 1970 (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0056)
    - Francis Leoni - "L'Oracolo", Undated (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0057)
    - "Police Song" 1/21/75 - part 1 only, Undated (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0058)
    - Sugimoto - interview at "Opening" 2/27/78 Roll #1, 1978 (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0059)
    - Sugimoto - interview at "Opening" 2/27/78 Roll #2, 1978 (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0060)
    - Sugimoto - interview at "Opening" 2/27/78 Reel #3, 1978 (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0061)
    - Sugimoto - interview at "Opening" 2/27/78 Reel #4, 1978 (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0062)
    - Visions (KCET) "Gold Watch" by Momoko Iko, Undated (Box 79, Reel ID: 292.0063)
    - Buddy Hackett - "Ting Me a Tong" and "Chinese Rock and Egg Roll" record, Undated; ID; 292.0064 (Box 79, Media ID; 292.0064)
      Format: 7" Vinyl Sound Recording (45 rpm)
    - "Tokyo Rose: Radio Traitor or Radion Patriot?", 1977; ID: 292.0065 (Box 79, Media ID: 292.0065)
      Format: 12" Vinyl Sound Recording (33 1/3 rpm)
    - Yellow Pearl - "I'm Alright Jack" and "We Are the Children" record, Undated; ID: 292.0066 (Box 79, Media ID: 292.0066)
  - Subseries C: Papers Removed from Audio
    - [Black Perspective on the News] - newspaper clipping, Undated (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0008a)
    - "Chinatown: A Place to Live" - NY Post clipping 4/18/78, 1978 (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0015a)
    - Cohen tape - [notes from interview] (Tapes 292.0016 & 292.0017), 1989 (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0016a)
    - Hiroshima - Nagasaki - program, 1972 (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0021a)
    - "How the West Was Won" newspaper clippings, 1979 (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0022a)
    - "Kung Fu" clipping, Undated (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0031a)
    - "Our Story" clipping, 1976 (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0035a)
    - "Year of the Dragon (Police Story)" clipping, 1975 (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0046a)
    - Asian American Reality Conference - index of speakers, 1970 (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0054a)
    - "Tokyo Rose: Radio Traitor or Radio Patriot?" data entry window print-out, 2002 (Box 40, Folder ID: 292.0065a)
- Series VIII: Video
  This series contains video material collected by Kishi. The VHS and BetaMax portions contain commercial videos, as well as movies and television shows recorded off of the TV, including titles such as "21 Jump Street" (1989), "China" (1943), "The Hanoi Hilton" (1987), "Old San Francisco" (1927), and "Vengeance of Fu Manchu" (1967). This series also contains videos of Kishi's "Scrutable Images" of Asians and Asian Americans. Many cassettes contain the original notations and descriptions within the case.
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - [H1], Undated; ID: 292.0067 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0067)
    Format: Umatic
  - KSP1, Undated; ID: 292.0068 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0068)
  - KSP2, Undated; ID: 292.0069 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0069)
  - KSP3, Undated; ID: 292.0070 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0070)
  - KSP4, Undated; ID: 292.0071 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0071)
  - KSP5, Undated; ID: 292.0072 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0072)
  - KSP6, Undated; ID: 292.0073 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0073)
  - KSP7, Undated; ID: 292.0074 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0074)
  - KSP8, Undated; ID: 292.0075 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0075)
  - KSP9, Undated; ID: 292.0076 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0076)
  - "Scrutable Images: A Century of Hollywood's Asian" (3/23/93), 1993; ID: 292.0077 (Box 80, Media ID: 292.0077)
  - VHS - A-I, c. 1927-2001 (Box 81)
    File Plan
    Format: VHS
  - VHS - J-W, c. 1927-2001 (Box 82)
  - Betamax - A-K, Undated (Box 83)
    Format: Betamax
  - Betamax - L-W, Undated (Box 84)
  - "Chinatown Nights", "The Chinese Americans", "The Mouthpiece","Tokyo Story", Undated (Box 84)
    Format: DVD
- Series IX: Film
  This series contains film reels of movies with Asian characters and themes.
  Film materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - "China: Land of My Father", 1984 (Box 85, Reel ID: 292.0078)
    Format: 16mm
  - "Feet of Mud", 1924 (Case 292.0079)
    Format: 8mm
  - "The Japanese American", Undated (Box 85, Reel ID: 292.0080)
  - "The Mission of Mr. Foo", 1915 (Case 292.0081)
  - "The Terror" reel 1 of 2, Undated (Box 86, Reel ID: 292.0082)
  - "The Terror" reel 2 of 2, Undated (Box 86, Reel ID: 292.0083)
- Series X: Collectibles
  This series contains statuettes, toys, games, and various other types of collectibles and objects collected by Yoshio Kishi.
  - "The Yellow Peril" Asian Woman figurine [candy dish?] - 1 metal, 1 ceramic, Undated (Box 54)
  - Asian Child statuette [Buddha?] with pillow - ceramic, Undated (Box 54)
  - Naked Chinese Man "Joss" statuette - alabaster, 1908 (Box 54)
  - Chinese Man Vase - ceramic, Undated (Box 54)
  - Halco American Ace Caps for Repeating Pistols, Undated (Box 54)
  - "Chop Suey: Steak - Best in Town" woodblock stamp, Undated (Box 54)
  - Asian Man and Woman [incense burner] - ceramic - with small wooden piece with Japanese writing inside, Undated (Box 55)
  - Bank of China - Asian Woman bobble head coin bank, 1970 (Box 55)
  - Asian Man polishing a rifle - statue - ceramic, Undated (Box 55)
  - Chinese Man with bag of rice - statue - ceramic, Undated (Box 55)
  - Framed wicker mat, Undated (Box 56)
  - Buttons / Pins, Undated (Box 56)
  - "The China Doll San Francisco: $3 All Night Check" coin, Undated (Box 56)
  - Round wall ornaments with Chinese boy - wood and enamel, Undated (Box 56)
  - Portrait of Chinese man in wicker frame, Undated (Box 56)
  - "Wonders of the Stereoscope" kit - cards, viewer, text, and plates, 1976 (Box 57)
  - Board of Global Misitries of the United Methodist Church - "The Asian American" teaching kit - booklet, record, and film strip, Undated (Box 57)
  - "Ethnic Studies Teacher Resource Kit" - books, tape, film strip, 1975 (Box 57)
  - "Prejudice in America: The Japanese Americans" Teaching kit - booklet, film strips, tapes, 1971 (Box 57)
  - GI Joe Classic Collection - 442nd Infantry, Nisei Soldier, Undated (Box 58)
  - High Adventure Cliffhangers: Buck Rogers, War Against the Han, 1993 (Box 58)
  - Illustrated picture of Asian man injecting an arm with a syringe, by Gahan Wilson - framed, Undated (Box 58)
  - Frosted Flakes Cereal box - with Toby Dawson, c. 2006 (Box 58)
  - Kashi Great Friends Cereal box - with Asian man and white woman, Undated (Box 58)
  - Special K Cereal box - with Kristi Yamaguchi, c. 1992 (Box 58)
  - Scrapbook of postcards and loose pages, Undated (Box 59)
  - Chinese Sex Girl - blow up doll, Undated (Box 60)
  - "Yellow Peril" art book of collected materials, Undated (Box 61)
  - "Mickey's World Tour" - Japan - Disney 120 piece jigsaw puzzle, Undated (Box 61)
  - Asian man hand puppet, Undated (Box 61)
  - Cherry Chan Candy - box, Undated (Box 61)
  - Russel Leong drawings on cards - blank, Undated (Box 61)
  - Japanese illustration - eraser set, 1999 (Box 61)
  - "Chinatown, USA" 1500 piece jigsaw puzzle, Undated (Box 62)
  - "La-Li-Luo Dance-Songs of the Chuxiong Yi, Yannan Province, China" - book and tape set, 1990 (Box 62)
  - "The Tables Turned: You Sabe Him? Kealney Must Go!" - framed illustration, Undated (Box 62)
  - "Yellow Peril" board game, Undated (Box 63)
  - "Team Spirit '88: Korea" photo album, 1988 (Box 63)
  - "James Clavell's Tai-Pan" board game, Undated (Box 64)
  - Fu Manchu Halloween Mask, Undated (Box 64)
  - "Ching-Ching 1888" framed illustration of performers (Box 65)
  - "Chinatown, NY" framed illustration by H.B. Doppel, Undated (Box 65)
  - Yellow Peril Challenge - A Solid Color Circular Nightmare - Jigsaw Puzzle, Undated (Box 65)
  - "Searching Chinese Immigrants for Opium, at San Francisco" from a Sketch by W.W. Bode, Harper's Weekly - framed, 1882 (Box 66)
  - "More Protection in a Free Country" - framed illustration, Undated (Box 66)
  - "Chinese Costumes Playing Cards" - two decks in a sealed box, Undated (Box 66)
  - We Wow Wang: A "Wow" of a Game, Undated (Box 66)
  - "Movie Cut-Ups" Madame Butterfly jigsaw puzzle, Undated (Box 66)
  - Newman's Own Low-Fat Sesame Ginger Salad Dressing - photocopy of full bottle, Undated (Box 67)
  - "A Series of 24 Chinese Scenes issued with 'My Princess' Cigarettes", Undated (Box 67)
  - Trade cards with images of Asians, Undated (Box 67)
  - Two illustrations of Chinese man playing / cheating at cards with white men - mounted on boards, Undated (Box 67)
  - "Victorian Valentine Tuck Chinaman Litho" cardboard cut-out, Undated (Box 67)
  - "Chop Suey" game, Undated (Box 68)
  - Stereoscope cards - "Siege of Port Arthur", Undated (Box 69)
  - Glass slides - "The Beggar Prince", "The Breath of the Gods", "The Courageous Coward", "Dinty", "A Heart in Pawn", and an unidentified portrait", Undated (Box 70)
- Series XI: Data Storage
  This series contains CD-ROMs holding material on Asian Americans.
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - The Anna May Wong Collection: 95 Photographs, Undated (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0001)
    Format: CD-ROM
  - Ansel Adams: Manzanar, Undated (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0002)
  - A/P/A Shipment 003 (Microsoft Word), Undated (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0003)
  - Early Films of San Francisco 1897-1916, 2002 (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0004)
  - Heritage Comics Interactive Catalog Disk - from "Catalogs and Price Lists: Heritage Comics" folder in Collecting series, 2002 (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0005)
  - History of the Moving Image, 1999 (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0006)
  - The Jack London Collection - photo gallery, 2001 (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0007)
  - "Mulan" (Disney) Multimedia CD-ROM press kit, Undated (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0008)
  - TH. Nast: His Period and Pictures 1903, by Albert Paine, Undated (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0009)
  - Travel and Exploration: Kings Photographic Views of New York City 1895, 1999 (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0010)
  - Vaudeville Films, vol. 1, 2002 (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0011)
  - World War II Films - The Japanese, Undated (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0012)
  - World War II Poster Art, Undated (Box 79, Disk ID: 292.3.0013)
- Oversize Series I: Asian Americans
  This series contains the oversize material from "Series I: Asian Americans".
  - Subseries A: Events and Organizations
    - Asian-American Film Festival - poster, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Asian American Film Festival, Twentieth Anniversary - poster, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Asian American International Film Festival - poster, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Basement Workshop poster, 1978 (Folder 2 Left)
    - "Celebrate Asian-Pacific American Heritage Week" poster, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Japan Film Week, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Serials
    - "Gidra" Magazine - The 20th Anniversary, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Subseries C: Activism
    - Basement Workshop calendar, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Subseries E: Crime
    - "Actual Detective Stories of Women in Crime" serial, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Chol Soo Lee Defense Committee - poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Defense of Chol Soo Lee - poster, Undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Oversize Series II: History and Politics
  This series contains the oversize material from "Series II: History and Politics".
  - Subseries A: Serials
    - Harper's Weekly - "Every Dog (no distinction of color) has his day" illustration; "A Diplomatic (Chinese) design presented to the U.S." illustration, 1879, 1881 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Pic Magazine, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Puck - "Keeping Account" illustration, 1885 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: US-Asia Relations
    - "China and America: A Look at a Long and Ambivalent Relationship" from The New York Times Magazine, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - "Current Situation in Communist China: A Briefing in Chart Form", 1990 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - "Free China Salutes the American Bicentennial" - New York Times, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - "Grand Pictorial Representation of the Procession up Broadway in Honor of the Arrival of the Japanese Embassy" - The New York Illustrated News, 1860 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - "History in Headlines of San Francisco", Undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - "This is Yokohama", 1971 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - "Too Many Shylocks" illustration in "Puck", 1901 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Union Label Department - "Made in Japan" poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Chinese Americans
    - "100 Years Before Me" - Chinese American History fill-in, c. 1976 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - "1982: Year of the Dog" calendar (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - "The Anti-Chinese Wall" illustration from Puck Magazine, Undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - "Certificate of Chinese Subjects of Exemption Class" for Henry Chee Young, 1916 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - China Today - photo exhibit, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - "Chinese Emigration to America..." engraving in Harper's Weekly, 1876 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - "Chinese in America: Images from a Neglected Past" exhibit poster, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - "A Chinese Reception in San Francisco" engraving from Harper's Weekly, 1877 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Harper's Weekly - "Chinese Highbinders" illustration, 1886 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Harper's Weekly - "The Chinese Question" illustration, 1871 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - "The Heathen Chinee" print, Undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Illustration of Chinese in America, Undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - "Plain Language from Truthful James" by Bret Harte - illustrated poem, 1871 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Sheet Music - "Me Be Like Mellican Man", 1882 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Sheet Music - Songs about Chinese, 1870-1927 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - "Underground Opium Den in San Francisco" engraving from Harper's Weekly, 1888 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - The Weekly Thunderbolt - Anti-Chinese illustration / article, 1888 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - "The Yellow Peril that We are All Afraid of" illustration, 1903 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Subseries D: Chinatowns
    - Chinatown Wax Museum, San Francisco - paper bag, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - "Human Smuggling in Chinatown" - Manhattan Spirit vol.8, no.13, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - "Official Map of Chinatown in San Francisco" photocopy, 1885 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Subseries E: Japanese Americans
    - "Abrogate U.S.-Japan Security Treaty" poster, Undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - All American Japanese 442 Battalion - poster, Undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - "Background Material for developing an illustrated discussion on the 1942 Japanese Relocation", Undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Chushingura on Stage and in Print - exhibit poster, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Civilian Exclusion Order no. 34, "Instructions to all Persons of Japanese Ancestry..." - notice, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Civilian Exclusion Order no. 34, "Instructions to all Persons of Japanese Ancestry..." - notice, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Civilian Exclusion Order no. 34, "Instructions to all Persons of Japanese Ancestry..." - notice (black background), 1942 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - "The Company You Keep" poem poster by Lanson Fusao Inada - signed, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - "A Conflagration in a Japanese City" engraving - Harper's Weekly, 1877 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - East Coast Japanese Americans for Redress - poster and maps, c. 1970 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Graphs, Facts, and Timelines of Japanese in Ameica, Undated (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - "Hiroshima and Nagasaki" exhibit poster, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - "Jap Rose Soap" advertisement in Ladies' Home Journal, 1919 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - "Japs Returning from Relocation Centers" illustration, Undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - "Lt. Gen. DeWitt's Order to Keep the Japs Away from the Coast" illustration (original), Undated (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - New York Hearing Committee on Wartime Relocation, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - The New York Times Magazine - "How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying" cover, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - "A Nikkei Legacy: Quilted Remembrance" poster - Asian American Art Show, Undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Nippon-Ten 79 - Japanese Art Show, Undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Sheet Music - Songs about Japanese, 1904 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - "Shinohara: Japan House Gallery" exhibition poster; "Tokyo Week in New York" poster, 1982, 1985 (Folder 16)
  - Subseries F: Asians and Asian Americans
    - "The Asian Campus" - New York Times, Education Life section, 2007 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - "Finding the Face of Asian NYC" - New York Press, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - "Jesse Jackson '88" poster - with Japanese writing attachement, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - New York Times Magazine - "The TV Peril" cover illustration, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - "Save the Boat People: Lights for Liberty" poster, Undated (Folder 3 Left)
- Oversize Series III: Curricular Studies
  This series contains the oversize material from "Series III: Curricular Studies".
  - Subseries B: Diversity in Education
    - East / West Activities Kit, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Oversize Series IV: Hollywood Films, Television, Theater and Actors
  This series contains the oversize material from "Series IV: Hollywood Films, Television, Theater, and Actors".
  - Subseries A: Film
    - "The Big Wave" movie poster, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - "Charlie Chan and the Curse of the Dragon Queen" movie posters, undated (Folder 3)
    - "China" movie poster, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - "China Girl" movie poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - "Chinatown Squad" movie poster, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - "The Chinese Bungalow" Film program, Undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - "Chinese Hercules" movie poster, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - CineVue Newsletter, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - CineVue Newsletter, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - CineVue Newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - CineVue Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - "The Crimson Kimono" - Columbia Pressbook, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - "Drums of Fu Manchu" movie poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - "El Mundo do Suzie Wong" movie poster (in Spanish), Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Flower Drum Song" movie poster, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - "Hell's Half Acre" movie poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - "Hell's Half Acre" movie poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Japanese Butterflies - film stills, Undated (Box 46, Folder 16)